goplextor.com 2019-03-28

# Plextor SSD Storage Solutions | Privacy Policy

### PRIVACY POLICY

* * *

Lite-On Technology Corporation respects our company websites users’ right of privacy. Please read carefully our company’s Privacy Policy below. We hope to let all visitors fully understand what data we collect, how we collect the data, and how we protect the right of privacy. 

If you continue to browse our company websites or if you provide us your private data, it will be regarded as your acceptance of the terms of our Privacy Policy.

#### Information We Collect

You do not have to provide any personal information while accessing our company’s websites. However certain services or functions of our websites may collect the personal information that can be used to identify the specific individual, such as your name, address, telephone number, email address or any other contact information.

Additionally, we may also automatically collect certain information incidental to your use of our websites, such as the IP address, the type of the browser software, and the operating system of the your computer, as well as the web page accessing information collected through Cookies or Web Beacon, such as the times of access, duration of use, etc.

#### How Will We Use Your Personal Information

The personal information we will collect may be used in responding to your requests, sending mail and newsletters, or providing the services per your request. We may also use part of the collected information to help improving the content and service quality of our websites.

We will not disclose, sell, provide or share your personal information to/with other persons or non-LiteOn-affiliates, except that (1) we need to provide the services at your request, (2) we already obtained your authorization, or (3) we have the following situations.

We may provide the part of the collected information to our management team and the authorized employees or affiliates relevant to the business as the reference (example: we may provide your resume information to our Human Resources Department for reference.), or we may use the authorized webpage design as the reference for the maintenance or enhancement of our company’s web. The provision of the above mentioned information must follow this Privacy Policy as well as other pertinent confidentiality and security measures. We may also disclose the collected personal information for the following reasons: (1) by law requirement; (2) to comply with legal process or governmental requests; (3) to respond the subpoenas or warrants served on LiteOn technology Corp.; (4) to protect and defend the rights or property of LiteOn Technology Corp.

#### Modification or Deletion of Your Personal Information

If you wish to modify your personal information, stop receiving information from us, or remove your personal information from our company website database, please mail to [](mailto:webmaster@liteon.com)webmaster@liteon.com and we will immediately handle it for you.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

LiteOn Technology Corp. may revise this Privacy Policy irregularly. You can ascertain that our Privacy Policy has been updated by examining “Last Revised Version and Date”. We suggest you irregularly visit our company website to review our latest Privacy Policy and its terms.

Last Revised Version：Version 2014-06-25
    Last Revised Date：07/30/2014

Copyright © 2015 Plextor All rights reserved.

Plextor branded products are developed and sold by Lite-On Technology Corporation.

Privacy Policy| Terms & Conditions
